宅度假胡子非常有型啊 老爸
That staycation beard's really taking shape, dad.
开始会黏吃的了
It's starting to trap food.
是啊
Yep.
已经从痒变得难受了
It's gone from itchin' to bitchin'.
你还在穿这身运动服
And you're still rocking the sweats.
一周都没换
Every day this week.
内裤都不换吗
Same underwear?
什么内裤
What underwear?
等下继续聊
Hold that thought.
还要继续聊吗
Do I have to?
菲城市长办公室
Mayor's office. City of Phila-Dunphy-a.
抱歉 我刚下班
I'm sorry. I just got done.
我的电脑坏了
My computer crashed,
共从台湾运来的四架板转轴
and we got four pallets of hinges from Taiwan
铆接又出了问题
with faulty riveting.
至少你的故事很吸引人[铆接]
At least your story's riveting.
好搞笑 等下给你解释
It's clever. I'll tell you later.
为什么小货车停在咱家停车道上
Hey, why is the minivan in the driveway?
你今天早上把我堵在里面了
You parked me in this morning.
我那时候开会快迟到了
I was running late for a meeting,
所以我就开了海莉的花冠去的
so I just took Haley's Corolla.
好玩
Fun.
要是闻起来不像
It would be if it didn't smell like
鲍勃·马利的洗衣篮那就真还不错
the inside of Bob Marley's laundry hamper.
总之我还得再打好几个电话
Anyway, I've got a bunch more calls to make.
今天晚上没时间做饭了
I'm not gonna have time to cook tonight.
我们可以去外面吃
We could go out.
新开了家餐馆叫滑板鞋
There's that new restaurant -- Sliders.
噱头就是餐馆开在一个斜坡上
The gimmick is they built it on a slant,
所有服务员都只穿袜子
and the waiters all wear socks.
听起来不怎么样啊
That doesn't sound good at all.
你能叫点外卖吗
Can you just order something?
好啊 没问题
Yeah, you got it.
太好了
Great.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
走开 小狗
Run away, little dog.
好吧 我绕开就是了
Fine. Go around you.
你不会走的
You're not gonna move.
因为我不会为你停车的
'Cause I'm not stopping for you.
我会为你停车的
I'm stopping for you.
该死
Damn.
快走啊
Move it!
真不走吗
Seriously?
别忘了客人来的时候 你要照看乔哦
Don't forget you have to watch Joe while we have company.
又要吗
Again?
对 又要
Yes, again.
有什么问题吗
What is the problem?
他老想看他的节目
He always wants to watch his show
《神秘孩纸》 是"纸"哦
"Mystery Kidz," With a "Z."
太让人受不了了
It's insufferable.
现在你明白
Now you know what I felt
我陪你看你最喜欢的节目时的感受了吧
when I had to watch your favorite show.
《经典剧场》吗
"Masterpiece Theater"?
节目主持人是一只可怕的木偶
It was hosted by a creepy puppet.
那是艾伦·卡明
That was Alan Cumming.
杰 你得再多搬两把椅子出来
Ay, Jay, you have to add two more chairs.
给谁
For who?
我们俩 麦克克劳兹夫妇 夏普斯夫妇
It's us, the McClouds, and the Sharps.
我还请了我朋友戴娜和她丈夫瑞斯
I also invited my friend Dana and her husband, Reece.
瑞斯 瑞斯是谁
Reece? Who's Reece?
我刚跟你说了啊 戴娜的老公
I just told you. Dana's husband.
我在家长教师联谊会午餐时认识她的
I met her at the PTA lunch,
她是反欺霸社团中唯一一个
and she's the only woman in the anti-bullying campaign
我不想揍的女人
that I don't want to punch in the face.
我为什么要请那俩人来我家里
Why would I want these people in my house
搅了我的扑克局
messing up my poker game?
这样你就可以认识新朋友了啊
Maybe you'll meet new friends.
我们以前就说过了啊 我不想认识什么新朋友
We've been over this before. I don't want any new friends.
我的朋友数量刚刚好
I have the exact-right number of friends.
杰 你的朋友都是
Jay, your friends have been around
从默片时代过来的了
since before the movies could talk.
我觉得开始找一些备胎
I don't think it's the worst idea
也不失为一个好主意
to start getting some backups.
老爸 什么是最小公分母[特征人群]啊
Hey, Daddy, what's a lowest common denominator?
-真人秀 -好好笑
- Reality TV. - That's hilarious,
但我明天要考试了
but I've got a quiz tomorrow.
什么声音
What is that noise?
我提醒你一下 已经有好几周
Let me remind you that it's been weeks
楼上没人租了
since we've had a tenant up there.
所以你就租给一个摇滚乐队
So you rented it to a rock band?
一个基督教摇滚乐队
A Christian rock band.
这下好了 所以他们又吵又爱评论人
Oh, good. Okay, so they're noisy and judge-y.
你和你这种狭隘的城市优越感太不要脸了
Shame on you and your narrow, big-city attitude.
我也认识很多有信仰的开明人士
I've known many accepting people of faith.
我被传教士追到了一片湖里
And I've been chased into a lake.
所以我们都有权维持自己的观点
So I guess we're both entitled to our opinion.
不
No!
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
进
Come in.
这是米奇尔 音乐太棒了
This is Mitchell, and the music sounds great.
就是想问问你们有没有可能稍微小点声
Just wondering if you could turn it down a-a skosh.
当然可以 很抱歉
Yeah, of course. We're sorry.
只是想给楼上的哥们感受一下我们的新歌
Just giving the guy upstairs a taste of our new song.
他是说上帝
He means God.
是吗 真的没有我不知道的三楼吗
Really? There's no third floor I don't know about?
顺便提一嘴 我们很喜欢这里
We love the place, by the way.
真的非常漂亮
It's just scrumptious.
很好 很好
Good! Good!
所以你们是基督教摇滚乐队是吧
So, you guys are a Christian rock band?
化水为酒乐队 没错 就是我们
Water to Wine. Yeah, that's us.
我希望你们不会把
Well, I hope you're not expecting
你们的粉丝们都带来这里吧
to bring all your groupies back here.
别担心
Don't worry.
羔羊教堂的士兵
The Soldiers of the Lamb Church
禁止婚前关系
forbids premarital relations.
当然 但是我也能想到几个
Of course. But I can think of a few ladies
在我们长老给过祝福后
I wouldn't mind multiplying with
我愿意与她生小孩的姑娘
after our elders give us their blessings.
我听到了哦
I heard that.
我们爱姑娘
We love girls!
正巧你们来了 我需要点外人的意见
As long as you guys are here, I need an outsider's opinion.
我在写一首歌
I'm working on a song,
但是这些家伙觉得这歌太温柔了
but these guys think it's too soft.
介意听一下吗
Do you mind?
来吧 兄弟
Lay it on us, bro.
*隐藏已久*
*Hiding for so long*
*不属于我的真实自我*
*The real me, I don't belong*
*我不是自己 从未曾是*
*I'm not myself, I never was*
*我在黑夜哭泣 都因为*
*I cry at night and all because*
*我困在一条秘密的小路中*
*I'm trapped on a secret path*
*我需要圣浴*
*I need a holy bath*
*洗刷我隐藏的罪孽*
*To wash away the sins I hide*
*浇熄我内心深处的小火焰*
*To douse the fire I feel inside*
该死 戴克斯 你这样我很不爽
Aw, dang it, Dex, you're bumming me out!
冷静 库普
Calm down, Coop.
我们进了城
Just 'cause we're in the city
不代表我们就能随心所欲说话
doesn't mean we got to talk like it.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你知道吗 戴克斯 我喜欢这首歌
You know what, Dex, I like that song.
是啊 歌名是什么
Yeah. What's the title?
我叫它《求助》
I call it "A Cry for Help."
-你听到了吗 -当然 我就在这呢
- Did you hear that? -Yeah, I'm standing right here.
你又回来了吗
You're back again?
我也想你了
Missed you, too.
桑杰这周末回家了
Sanjay's home this weekend.
今天是我们一个重要的日子 一周年纪念日
It's kind of a big day for us -- our first anniversary.
看看我给他准备了什么
Look what I got him.
这是一支鸭嘴龙掌骨
It's a hadrosaur metacarpal
他喜欢收集恐龙骨头
for his dinosaur bone collection.
太过了吗
Too much?
如果你们都是正常人这是什么等级的礼物
Well, what's the equivalent gift if you guys were normal?
是星巴克礼品卡还是劳力士
Like, a Starbucks card or a Rolex?
大概相当于一架很棒的显微镜吧
Kind of like a really nice microscope.
说了也白说
You're not helping.
我还以为书呆子的周年纪念应该是呼吸器
I thought the gift for a first nerd anniversary was inhaler.
你们老爸呢
Where's your dad?
在楼上 怎么了
Upstairs. Why?
你给我们买了狗
You got us a dog?!
不 它只是迷路了
No, no! It's a stray,
我们不会留下它的
and we are not keeping him.
安静点
Be quiet.
别让你们老爸知道
Your dad cannot know he's here.
他要是看到一定会喜欢上它
If he sees him, he'll get all attached,
我们就不可能把它送走了
and there's no getting rid of it.
就跟卢克一样
Oh, it'll be like Luke all over again.
至少他们有我的时候已经结婚了
At least they were married when they had me.
你毁了妈妈的生活
You ruined mom's life.
停 我现在很高兴有你们
Stop. I am now very happy I have all of you.
可是我没办法再多照顾一个生物了
But I just can't take care of another living creature.
那你为什么还带它回家
Then why'd you bring it home?
我没法把它留在街上
I couldn't leave it in the street.
克莱尔 是你吗
Claire, is that you?
照顾好它
Take care of it.
我不会把狗狗养死的
I'm not gonna kill a dog.
把它藏进你房间
Hide it in your room.
是像我想的一样吗
Is that what I think it is?
不是
Uh, no.
没错 披萨到了
Yeah, pizza's here.
你好
How you doing?
你们干嘛呢
What was that?
我是披萨怪
I'm the pizza monster!
这是我的新角色
It's this new character I'm doing.
我喜欢 我真的很喜欢
I love it. I really love it.
我其实不怎么喜欢
I didn't really love it.
感觉跟我的"鸡锅海盗"有点像
It felt a little close to my Chicken Pot Pirate.
那是个不解之谜
It's a mystery.
那是谁
Who's that?
诺尼 可以隐身
Noni. She can be invisible.
那又是谁
Who's that?
勾勾
Gogo.
他能跳下高楼
He can jump off of buildings.
这是我看过最不现实的节目
This is the most unrealistic show I've ever seen.
那又是谁
Who's that?
是 太好了 我现在开大门
Yes, great. I will open the gate.
瑞斯 可能连修门都不会
Reece. Probably can't even work a gate.
你可能会喜欢他
Maybe you'll like him.
他是国王的牙医
He's the Kings' dentist.
那我还是皇帝的橱柜制造商呢
Well, hoity-toity. I'm the emperor's closet maker.
洛杉矶国王冰球队
The L.A. Kings hockey team.
国王的牙医 为什么他要这么说
Kings' dentist. Why does he say it like that?
因为这样听起来很酷炫吗
What, is he trying to be all fancy?
他什么都没说 是我说的
He didn't say anything. I said it.
-你好 -你好
- Hello. - Hi.
戴娜 瑞斯 这是我先生杰
Dana, Reece, this is my husband, Jay.
-你好 瑞斯 -你好 杰
- Hi, Reece. How are you? - Hey, Jay.
戴娜 跟我来厨房吧
Dana, come with me to the kitchen
让男生们互相了解一下
while the boys get to know each other.
好
All right.
你听说了吗
Did you hear they're thinking
他们在考虑在学校里禁脏话
of eliminating cursive at the school?
所有脏话 还是艹字头那个
All of it, or just the "F" Word?
我给你带了瓶威士忌
I brought you some Scotch.
这瓶是好酒 谢谢
That's quite a bottle. Thank you.
歌洛莉亚跟我说你是国王队的牙医
Gloria tells me you're the Kings' dentist.
你提到这个的态度感觉好拽
Well, when you say it like that, it sounds so hoity-toity.
不如把酒开了吧
Why don't we crack that open?
你这有古巴高希霸罗拔图雪茄吗
And do you have any Cohiba Robustos?
我也想有 可是这牌子基本找不到了
Oh, I wish, but, you know, they're impossible to find.
瞧瞧看
Well, look at that.
我刚找到两支
I just found two.
好吧 这人还挺不错的
Okay, the guy wasn't all bad,
可我不能让歌洛莉亚知道
but I couldn't let Gloria know
不然她就会开始逼我去做一大堆
or it would open the door for a whole bunch of new things
我不想做的事
I don't want to do --
比如试新餐厅
Trendy restaurants,
关于女性一些无聊事情感觉的电影
movies about how women feel about crap.
谁需要那些啊
And who needs it?
如果这周还不够惨的话
As if this week wasn't bad enough,
我们在布鲁塞尔的硬件供应商又变卦了
now my hardware supplier in Brussels is flip-flopping.
看来你最近吉卦不怎么多啊
Sounds like you're dealing with a real Belgian waffle.
那是狗叫吗
Is that a dog?
什么 不是
What? No.
听起来像狗叫
That sounds like a dog.
为了不听我说话
You will do anything
你什么事情都做得出来 对吗
to avoid hearing me talk about work, won't you?
我要下楼冷静一下
I'm -- I'm just gonna go cool off downstairs. Yep.
亲爱的
Honey?
她说的没错
She is right.
有时候我不想听她说话
Sometimes I don't listen.
她是这么说的对吧 我不听她说话
That's what she said, right? I don't listen?
你怎么出来了
Did you get out?
快过来
Oh, come on, now.
亲爱的
Honey?
甜心
Sweetheart?
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
没关系 菲尔 你回去睡吧
It's fine, Phil, really. Just go back to bed.
我只是需要一点时间静一静
I just... need some time to myself.
你一哭我也想哭了
Y-You know I cry when you cry.
我会上楼的
I'll be upstairs.
你没事吧
You okay?
只是 最近太多事了
It's just -- It's been a lot.
我爱你
I love you.
戴克斯 你好吗
Hey, Dex. How are you?
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事 在欣赏你们的花园而已
Yeah, I was just admiring your garden.
快进来吧
Hey, come on in.
其他人呢
So, uh, where is the rest of the gang?
参加祷告晨跑了
Oh, they're out on a prayer jog.
我不太喜欢
It's not really my thing.
会经常发生吗
Is -- Is that something that happens a lot
你觉得自己格格不入的情况
where -- where you feel different?
你好吗 德克斯
Hi, Dex.
米奇尔
Hey, Mitchell.
能不能过来帮我个忙 很快就好
Can I have you help me over here for just a second?
好吧
Uh, okay.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
他明摆着想寻求帮助
He was clearly reaching out.
他在欣赏我们的花园
He was admiring our garden.
没人会欣赏我们的花园
Nobody admires our garden.
里面只有颗粘着购物袋的死仙人掌
It's a dead cactus with a grocery bag stuck to it.
你怎么回事
What is going on with you?
你不是一直不想
You're the one who never wants
掺和别人的生活吗
to get involved in people's lives.
你看不出来吗
Don't you see?
他觉得被那些人困住了
He feels trapped by those guys.
那些借《圣经》的名义干涉别人生活的坏蛋吗
Oh, the big, bad Bible thumpers?
又来了
Here we go again.
我只是说可以把他的歌
I'm just saying you could read his song
《求助》
"A Cry for Help"
解读成是求助
as a cry for help.
米奇尔 你被传教士逼到湖里去了
Mitchell, I'm sorry you got chased into a lake,
我认识的一些最善良最有爱
but some of the kindest, most loving,
最慷慨的人都是信教的
generous people I've ever known were churchgoers.
我就...
Just...
别...
Come --
戴克斯 我能不能发表一下个人见解
Hey, Dex, do you mind if I make a personal observation?
如果是想说我的翘臀 怪我妈咯
If it's about my hips, blame my mother.
不 不
No, no.
是关于你昨天唱的歌
It's -- It's about the song that you sang yesterday.
你似乎是想表达
It seemed like you were trying to express something --
你的感受
some feelings you might be having
而这些感受似乎
that you think might not be met with approval
没有被你们的"小团体"认可
from your..."community."
或者就只是首歌
Or it's just a song.
跟他自身情况毫无关联
Has nothing to do with his personal situation.
不 是有关联的
No, it does.
不好意思 你的痛是真真切切的
I'm -- I'm sorry. Your pain is real.
我只是觉得好有负罪感
I just feel so guilty.
我知道大家会很失望
I know people will be disappointed.
别 别 不要有负罪感
No, no, don't feel guilty.
听着 第一步就是要大声说出来
Look, the first step is to say it out loud.
我不想当鼓手
I don't want to be a drummer.
好 继续说
Okay, now say the other thing.
我不想再呆在乐队里了
I don't want to be in a band anymore.
我好想家
I miss home.
好想我的女友
I miss my girlfriend.
-抱歉 什么 -抱歉 你的什么
- I'm sorry. Whoa. What? - I'm sorry. Your what?
感觉心里一下释然了
It's like a weight has been lifted.
太感谢你们了
Thank you so much, guys.
我今天本想呆在里面的
You know, I was just gonna stay inside today,
还好出来了
but I'm really glad I came out.
他才不是想说那些
He doesn't get to say that.
乔
Oh, hey, Joe.
现在在播新一集《神秘孩纸》
Uh, there's a new "Mystery Kidz" on.
我不看了 谢谢
No, thanks.
"我不看了 谢谢"
"No, thanks"?
你难道不好奇谁偷了普可的魔法翅膀吗
Aren't you curious who stole Poco's magic wings?
没什么兴趣
Not really.
可是每个人都有嫌疑
But everyone's a suspect.
钟表匠讨厌普可
The watchmaker hates Poco,
布丁市长会不惜一切手段留任
and Mayor Pudding would do anything to stay in office.
你怎么会不想看接下来发生了什么呢
How could you not want to see what happens?
喂
Hello?
对 等等
Uh, yes. Hold on.
杰 是瑞斯
Jay, it's Reece.
你看 歌洛莉亚
You see, Gloria?
现在他开始给我打电话了
Now he's calling me.
我怕的就是这个
This is what I was afraid of.
他打电话来了
He called.
我的新朋友打电话了
My new friend called.
要带我去看冰球比赛
He's taking me to a hockey game.
太棒了
Great.
现在我非得跟瑞斯去一个什么无聊的慈善活动
Now I'm stuck going to some boring charity event with Reece.
你看你妈给我惹的好事
You see what your mom got me into?
杰 别这样 开明点
Jay, come on. Keep an open mind.
我们只是觉得要给瑞斯一个机会
All we're saying is give Reece a chance.
雷克斯
Rex.
史都比
Scooby.
克利福德
Clifford.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
猜它的名字
Trying to figure out his name.
你考虑过老爸吗
What about Dad?
给 老爸
Here, Dad.
不是
Nope.
不用猜他的名字
You do not need to figure out his name
因为我们要去贴启示
because we're going to put these fliers up,
就会有人打电话来了
and someone's gonna call.
我给桑杰的恐龙化石呢
What happened to the dinosaur bone I got for Sanjay?
我看到史努比
I saw Snoop...
在后院埋东西
burying something in the backyard.
你什么都没做吗
And you didn't do anything?
我帮它开了门
I opened the door for him.
那块化石有6500万年的历史
That bone lasted 65 million years,
在这个家居然撑不过一天
and it can't even last one day in this house?!
-克莱尔 -我的天 你爸来了
- Claire. - Oh, my God, your father!
狗 带出去 出去
The dog -- outside! Outside! Outside!
怎么了 亲爱的
Yeah, honey?
甜心 昨晚的事
Sweetheart, about last night.
我没用这俩耳朵认真听你说话
Because I didn't listen with these two ears...
对
Yes.
我想用这些郁金香[俩嘴唇]道歉
I want to apologize with these tu-lips.
太... 你太好了
Oh, that is very -- That's so sweet of you.
谢谢你 宝贝
Thank you, baby.
太好了 那是玉米片渣吗
Great. Oh, is that a tortilla chip right there?
就那
Yeah --
你好吗 昨天的朋友
Hola, amigo from yesterday.
你不会要吃吧
You're not gonna eat that, are you?
才不 多恶心
No, that would be disgusting.
这是啥
What are these?
那个是 是
Oh, that's a -- It's a...
蛋白质零食
It's a protein snack.
不喜欢的话就别吃了
You don't have to eat that if you don't like it.
不会
No.
我喜欢 好吃
I like it. Good.
有肝味[活力]
It's -- It's liver-y.
你太会照顾我们了
You take such good care of us.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thanks, honey.
我们应该把花放到花瓶里
We should get those flowers in a a vase.
不 菲尔
No, Phil.
别用那个花瓶
Not that vase.
看着我
Look at me!
好好看着我
Really look at me.
我觉得我在看啊
I feel like I am.
你还是不明白 对吧
You're just not getting it, are you?
对不起 我想一个人待会
I'm sorry. I need some alone time.
抱歉一直敲你家门
Sorry for knocking on your door so persistently,
可我们找不到戴克斯了
but we can't find Dex,
他的行李也不见了
and all his matching luggage is gone.
你们知道他去哪了吗
Do you have any idea where he is?
我... 我不知道 米奇尔
I don-- I don't know, Mitchell.
最后跟他说话的是你吧
Weren't you the last person to talk to him?
我们的时间不多了
And we haven't got much time.
要是我们没有鼓手
If we don't have a drummer,
就得被迫取消演出
we're gonna have to cancel the gig.
我主行事 凡人莫测
Well, the Lord works in mysterious ways.
-打住... -我...
- Don't even... - I...
真是毁灭性打击
Aah, this is devastating.
如果我们不演出 就拿不到报酬
If we don't play, we won't get paid,
也就没有足够的钱回家了
and we don't have enough money to get home.
你们不明白戴克斯正在经历什么
Hey, you don't know what Dex is going through.
人务须遵从本性
One hath to be true to the way one was born.
得了 你不能随便加个"务须"
Okay, you can't just add "Hath"
就假装是《圣经》里的话
and pretend it was in the Bible.
我想我们得打电话给音乐厅取消演出了
Well, I guess we better call the venue and cancel the gig.
天啊 好了 你懂的
Oh, boy, well, you know.
我可以做你们的鼓手
I could be your drummer.
上帝啊 又来了
Oh, God, here we go.
真的吗 你会打鼓
Really? You play?
我对上面那位发誓
Swear to G-dash-D.
来几段音乐试试 我能跟上节奏
Just play me a few bars. I can pick it up, follow along.
卡梅伦先生 太感谢你了
Mr. Cameron, thank you so much.
你让我想起某个重要的人
You kind of remind me of another special someone
他曾为我们做出重大牺牲
who made a pretty big sacrifice to save us.
拜托 别把我比作你的...
Please, do not compare me to your...
是伯尼·考夫曼先生 我们的经纪人
Mr. Bernie Kaufman, our manager.
他烧了他的鞋店[骗保险]赞助我们首张唱片小样
He burnt down his shoe store to pay for our first demo.
你在干嘛呢
what are you doing?
天啊 你快把狗抱走
Oh, God, you take the dog,
我把这收拾干净 好吗
and I'll clean this up, okay?
好
Okay.
亲爱的 我找了几个备选花瓶
Honey, I got some vase options.
怎么回事
What happened?
你觉得是怎么回事
what do you think happened?
我觉得她认为送花道歉
I think she saw those flowers as the shallow
是种肤浅的行为
transparent gesture they were
她有理由一气之下把它们撕烂
and shredded them to pieces in a justifiable rage.
没错
Yep.
我做了什么事让她这么生气
What have I done to upset her so much?
也许你照照镜子
Maybe you should look in a mirror
就能回答自己的问题了
and ask yourself that question.
我的老天啊 瞧我变成什么人了
Sweet Teen Wolf, what have I become?
看见那家伙了吗
You see that guy?
我在他的牙上下了不少功夫
I have done so much work on his mouth
花费足够付我船上的热水浴缸
that he's paid for the hot tub on my boat.
科皮塔刚才是跟你招手吗
Did Kopitar just wave to you?
那可不
It's the least he can do.
这周末我要带他去卡特琳娜钓鱼
I'm taking him out fishing this weekend in Catalina.
你想来吗
Hey, hey, do you want to come?
天啊 我当然很愿意去
Oh, my God, I'd love to go.
-不过... -怎么了
- Oh, but... - What?
昨晚你来之前
Last night, before you got there,
歌洛莉亚和我大吵了一架
Gloria and I got in a big to-do
因为我不想认识新朋友
about me not needing new friends.
现在你不愿意承认自己错了
And now you don't want to admit you were wrong.
你真懂我
Wow, do you get me.
这会儿应该是观赏鲸鱼的好天气
Well, it's supposed to be perfect whale-watching weather,
还有 对了
and, uh, oh, yeah,
格雷斯基也会来
Gretzky's coming, too.
有名的那个吗
The Great One?
他不跟人分享望远镜 这点倒臭名昭著
Not at sharing the binoculars, he isn't.
真要命 我去不了
It's killing me I can't go!
我有个疯狂的主意
Well, here's a crazy idea.
你干嘛不对你妻子实话实话
Why don't you tell your wife the truth
承认你错了
and admit you were wrong?
你没我想的那么懂我
You don't get me like I thought you did.
要不然呢
Or...?
好吧 我会跟她说实话的
Fine. I'll level with her.
你是怎么回事啊
What is going on?
太好了 不是老爸
Ohh, good, you're not Dad.
你和桑杰进展得怎么样
So, how'd it go with Sanjay?
他记得你们的纪念日吗
Did he remember your anniversary?
你说呢
You tell me.
我把化石送给他之后
After I gave him the fossil,
他给了我这只箱子作为斯坦福浪漫周末的礼物
he gave me this for romantic weekends up at Stanford.
看起来像是二手货
It looks kind of used.
你觉得有没有可能他忘了
Do you think it's possible he forgot
只是随手拿了一件东西...
and just grabbed the first thing that he's...
闭嘴 他爱我的
Shut up! He loves me!
真不敢相信连一个电话都没有
I can't believe i haven't gotten a single call.
我已经贴出无数启示了
I must have put up a thousand fliers.
大伙好啊
Hey, guys.
亲爱的
Honey.
-克莱尔 -在
-Claire. -Yeah.
我想跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我不听你说话
I don't listen.
光想靠送花解决问题
I try to solve problems with flowers.
还在朋友面前捏造你的负面形象
I do unflattering impressions of you for my friends.
最糟糕的是 我放任自己
And worst of all, I let myself go.
所以我刮了胡子 换了衣服
So I shaved and put on a suit.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
那是什么
What's that?
什么
What?
天啊 你收拾了行李
Oh, my God. You packed a suitcase.
你要离开一段时间
You need some time away.
我想我做这一切都...
I guess all this was...
太不够了 也太迟了
too little, too late.
但不包括美黑 做得时间太长 也太黑
Well, not the spray tan. That was too much, too long.
我觉得那个喷嘴坏了
I think the nozzle was broken.
你全都理解错了 都是我不好
You're getting this all wrong, and it's all my fault.
好吧 听着
Okay, look,
我一直拼命躲着你 没错
I have been trying to distract you, yes,
可那是因为我一直在想着对我有好处的事
but because I have been thinking about what was good for me
而不是可能会对你有好处的事
and not what might be good for you.
我不知道
So I have no idea
我们能不能找到它真正的主人
if we're ever gonna find out who his real owner is,
如果找不到的话 你可以养着它
but if we don't, you can keep him.
我为什么要养唐克斯里家的狗
Why would I want the Tanksley's dog?
你说什么
What?
这是巴迪
This is Buddy.
你不知道唐克斯一家搬去克里夫顿了吗
You know the Tanksley's over on Clifton?
我卖掉了他们的房子
I sold them their house.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
不过如果你同意我养宠物的话
But if you're open to me getting a pet...
当然同意 养只狗吧
Yeah. Of course. Get a dog.
不 我不想养狗
No, I don't want a dog.
我想养只凤头鹦鹉带去滑旱冰
I want a cockatoo to take Rollerblading.
想象一下 有只凤头鹦鹉站在我肩膀上
How cool would that be sitting on my shoulder
我的衬衫迎风飘动 那得多酷啊
my half shirt flapping in the wind?
你不能养鸟
You're not getting a bird.
-你是认真的吗 -是
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
那些养鸟的人
People that have birds
让鸟站在他们肩膀上到处走
and walk around with them on their shoulders --
他们看起来太可笑了
They look ridiculous.
那完全是为了吸引别人的注意而用力过度
It's obviously a desperate cry for attention.
好吧
Okay.
现在轮到我需要时间静静了
Now I need some time to myself.
你在看什么
What are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
你在看《神秘孩纸》
You're watching "Mystery Kidz."
你不是说不想看吗
You said you didn't want to.
是不想跟你一起看 你问题太多了
Not with you. You ask too many questions.
你这么说很过分
That's rude.
我可是出于礼貌才看的
I was only watching as a courtesy.
刚发生什么了
What just happened?
等等 那是谁
Wait, who's that?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
慈善会怎么样
How was the charity event?
我有话跟你说
I have to talk to you about something.
怎么了
What?
我要跟你说声对不起
I owe you an apology.
我这周末要去克利夫兰
I have to go to Cleveland this weekend
参加一个姑妈的葬礼
for my Aunt Bea's funeral.
很慈祥的一个老太太
Nice old lady.
她从悬崖上摔下去了
Fell off a cliff.
我和你一起去 我马上去收拾行李
I'll -- I'll go with you. I'll start packing right now.
不 你跟乔和曼尼留在这儿
No, no, no. You stay here with Joe and Manny.
我会寄个雪花玻璃球给你
I'll send you a snow globe.
我们有多余的望远镜吗
Hey, did we have an extra pair of binoculars?
我看到外面有只奇怪的鸟
I saw a weird bird outside.
别再撒谎了
Stop with the lies.
我真搞不懂男人
I really don't understand men.
你就不能直接承认你错了吗
Why can't you just admit that you were wrong?
这又不是缺点
It's not a weakness.
这是个优点
It's a strength,
我会因此更爱你 更尊重你
and I would love you and respect you more.
好吧
Fine.
我喜欢瑞斯 我想和他出去玩[私奔]
I like Reece, and I want to go away with him.
我就知道
I knew it!
我是对的 你是错的
I was right, and you were wrong!
从现在开始 我们要不断尝试新事物
From now on, we're gonna do new things all the time.
明天我们去埃塞俄比亚餐厅吃饭
Tomorrow we're going to an Ethiopian restaurant,
然后去看部电影
and then we're gonna watch a movie
那电影讲述了一封迟到30年的情书
about a love letter that arrived 30 years late
改变了两个女人一生的故事
and changed the life of two women.
我能带上瑞斯吗
Can I bring Reece?
不行
No!
大家好 我们来一起做表演前祷告吧
Hey, everyone, let's gather for the preshow prayer.
就像麦当娜和她的伴舞们一样
Kind of like Madonna and her backup dancers.
米奇尔先生 你想和我们一起吗
Mr. Mitchell, would you like to join us?
不用了 谢谢
Oh, I'm good. Thank you.
好的
All right.
仁慈的上帝
Heavenly Father,
请保佑我们的粉丝万分喜爱今晚的演出
we ask that you make this show super-amazing for all of our fans,
我们还要为戴克斯祈祷
and we pray for Dex.
上帝 请引导他
Lord, please guide him.
给他力量
Give him strength.
让他知道无论如何我们都爱他 接受他
And let him know that we love and accept him no matter what.
米奇尔 你听到了吗
Mitchell, did you hear that?
我要加入祷告
Hey, you know what? Let me in there.
我以前有些武断 对吗
I have been a little judgmental, haven't I?
所以
So...
请继续
Go ahead.
-阿门 -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
我们上台吧
Let's do this.
-祝你们好运 -谢谢
- Break a leg! - Thank you!
给你
Here.
这是什么
What's this?
如果你有兴致
If the mood strikes you,
何不跟我们一起上台
why don't you join us onstage,
制造些欢快的声音
make some joyful noise?
女士们先生们 有请化水为酒乐队
Ladies and gentlemen, Water to Wine!
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
*世界也许是平的*
*The world may be flat*
*但它总在变化*
*But it's always changin'*
*言语中罪恶在蔓延*
*So many sins from topics that are rangin' *
*魔鬼用毕早餐 恶性在肆虐*
*Devil's done with breakfast, and his evil is ragin' *
*这就是为什么 这就是为什么*
*Which is why. Which is why*
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*
*地狱中在开派对*
*There's a party in hell*
*酒一直在流淌*
*And the drinks are always flowing*
*我想我们认识所有参加派对的人*
*I think we all know the kind of people that are going*
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*
*除非他们相爱*
*Unless they really love each other*
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*
*我所认识的耶稣博爱世人*
*The Jesus I know loves everyone*
*不管你是直是弯*
*Even if you're gay or straight*
*不在乎你性取向如何*
*Doesn't matter about your sexuality-y-y*
我只是说也许
I'm just saying that maybe,
法国革命之前
before you join the French resistance,
一个人才可以走十几米去邻居家
you walk the 15 feet to your neighbor's house
问问她是否收到过自己的一封情书
and ask her did she get your damn love letter.
某些人说了
For someone that says
不想谈论电影
that they don't want to talk about the movie,
但你刚刚谈的不是电影是什么
that's all you seem to be talking about.
至少那电影
I think it's better
要比把这坨黄黄的糊塞进嘴里强
than putting this yellow mush in my mouth.
如果你能摒弃成见
Yeah, maybe if you opened up your mind,
你会发现其实这些很美味
you would see that this is actually delicious.
其实难吃极了
It was disgusting,
但我不能让杰知道他是对的
But I can never let Jay know that he is right.
食物难吃极了 但老实说
The food is terrible and if I'm being honest,
电影我还挺喜欢的
the movie sort of stays with me.